<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.7">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://stingerstories.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://stingerstories.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-10-03T05:30:05-05:00</updated><id>http://stingerstories.com/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Stinger Stories</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Listen</title><link href="http://stingerstories.com/Listen" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Listen" /><published>2020-09-19T01:01:01-05:00</published><updated>2020-09-19T01:01:01-05:00</updated><id>http://stingerstories.com/Listen</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://stingerstories.com/Listen">&lt;p&gt;Do you hear the crying?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;      In the streets weeping comes from&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;      burning rubber, broken glass, twisted metal.&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Believers know that this is The End;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;they are trapped on earth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;      Locked out of salvation they weep,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;      abandoned along with the sinners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world laments as unspeakable things stir,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;leaving their dark hidden places.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;      The hospitals are full,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;      But the ambulances won’t stop coming in,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Listen to the pain of a helpless world&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hear their sorrow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can’t ignore it.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Bevin Torres</name></author><category term="story" /><category term="scifi" /><category term="distopian" /><summary type="html">Do you hear the crying?       In the streets weeping comes from       burning rubber, broken glass, twisted metal.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Insurrection</title><link href="http://stingerstories.com/Insurrection" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Insurrection" /><published>2020-09-19T01:01:01-05:00</published><updated>2020-09-19T01:01:01-05:00</updated><id>http://stingerstories.com/Insurrection</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://stingerstories.com/Insurrection">&lt;p&gt;“We know what must be done,” I said to the congregated toys. “Never again!”&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Commando Joes, from the neighboring city of Marvinsroom, had made a beer can tower and secured a kitchen knife. I, Princess Alberta, would lead the charge. The stuffed animal army waited in ambush with scissors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“He’s coming!” said Binocular Soldier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Chloe,” the stepfather slurred to our sleeping child, “I’m sorry. Just one more time…”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Never again!” I cried, raising the knife.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Joshua Jones</name></author><category term="story" /><summary type="html">“We know what must be done,” I said to the congregated toys. “Never again!”</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">History Repeating</title><link href="http://stingerstories.com/History-Repeating" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="History Repeating" /><published>2020-09-19T01:01:01-05:00</published><updated>2020-09-19T01:01:01-05:00</updated><id>http://stingerstories.com/History-Repeating</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://stingerstories.com/History-Repeating">&lt;p&gt;It was the thirty-seventh day of new-September, only another seven until payday. Crew Boss Tyrell Vargas watched the least competent member of his squad almost sever his air hose and blow them all to hell and back.&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Concentrate,” he roared through the comm-link, “or you’re fired. Last warning – I won’t tell you again.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On this job, that meant a one way ticket off this gods forsaken hole of a planet, fired from the mouth of an anti-matter cannon. His employers had heard all about rights for their workers and wanted nothing to do with them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His boot stirred the ochre colored dust and revealed a few shards of pottery, remnants from the last civilization to rise and fall thousands of years before humans launched themselves into space. Ares Nine had not always been a dead world and something spoke to Vargas every night, whispering in an unfamiliar language when sleep would not come – the urgency in its tone clear even if he had no idea what it said. A dormant psychic ability, above average grade according to the corps assessment, meant that ghosts of the past swarmed around him like asteroid miners given a thirty-eight hour pass. They tried to give him a message, only a lingering trace of disquiet remained when the morning shift began. Why did it feel so much like a warning?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>R S Pyne</name></author><category term="story" /><summary type="html">It was the thirty-seventh day of new-September, only another seven until payday. Crew Boss Tyrell Vargas watched the least competent member of his squad almost sever his air hose and blow them all to hell and back.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Fwd:Do Not Forward</title><link href="http://stingerstories.com/Fwd-Do-No-Forward" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Fwd:Do Not Forward" /><published>2020-09-11T01:01:01-05:00</published><updated>2020-09-11T01:01:01-05:00</updated><id>http://stingerstories.com/Fwd-Do-No-Forward</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://stingerstories.com/Fwd-Do-No-Forward">&lt;p&gt;From: “Marion Yearwood” &amp;lt;lastcosmonaut.3000@ISStationmail.com4&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sent: Saturday, August 28, 2066, 12:08 PM IST&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To: “Dave Yearwood” &amp;lt;astrohusband33@hotmail.com4&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Subject: Fwd:Do Not Forward [Confidential]
&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FYI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From: “ISS CFO” &amp;lt;ISSstationCFO@ISStationmail.com4&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sent: Tuesday, August 17, 2066 3:48 PM IST&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To: “Marion Yearwood” &amp;lt;lastcosmonaut.3000@ISStationmail.com4&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CC: “ISS Accounting” &amp;lt;ISS.Accounting@ISStationmail.com4&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Subject: Do Not Forward [Confidential]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Cpt. Yearwood,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope this email finds you well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ve reviewed your request for an atmosphere with 21% O2, unfortunately, the Station’s Accounting department is currently unable to process these requests due to a significant backlog in terrestrial requests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Until they are able to review your request—estimated two weeks minimum—we hope that the current levels (17%, right?) will be sufficient. I know this was not the reply that you were hoping for, but please understand that we are working around the clock down here to maintain systems that were never intended to sustain life for more than a few 1000 years. Consider yourself lucky that you’re up there!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the meantime, we ask that you do not remove your health monitoring vest for any reason.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All the best,
Cmdr. Brad V. Bradley
Terrestrial CFO, International Space Station
“Always shoot for the moon. Even if you miss, you’ll end up among the stars.” -Janis Bradley, age 9&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sent from my iWatch&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>D. S. G. Burke</name></author><category term="story" /><category term="scifi" /><category term="distopian" /><summary type="html">From: “Marion Yearwood” &amp;lt;lastcosmonaut.3000@ISStationmail.com4&amp;gt; Sent: Saturday, August 28, 2066, 12:08 PM IST To: “Dave Yearwood” &amp;lt;astrohusband33@hotmail.com4&amp;gt; Subject: Fwd:Do Not Forward [Confidential]</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Where to Submit Short Stories</title><link href="http://stingerstories.com/where-to-submit-short-stories" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Where to Submit Short Stories" /><published>2020-09-06T01:01:01-05:00</published><updated>2020-09-06T01:01:01-05:00</updated><id>http://stingerstories.com/where-to-submit-short-stories</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://stingerstories.com/where-to-submit-short-stories">&lt;p&gt;You’ve put in the time to write, edit, and re-edit your masterpiece. In the process you have consumed more coffee than you care to admit. Now the hard part - finding the perfect publication to submit your short story.&lt;!--more--&gt; Fortunately, we have put together a list of our favorite online magazines and databases to help you find the perfect home for your brainchild.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Databases of publications&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://thegrinder.diabolicalplots.com/&quot;&gt;The Submission Grinder&lt;/a&gt; is a completely free-to-use database of thousands of online publications (both paid and unpaid). The search feature does a great job of narrowing down your target magazines based on genre and wordcound, and you can even track your stories statuses through the submission process if you create an account (again, free!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Writing Forums&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.sffchronicles.com/&quot;&gt;SFF Chronicles&lt;/a&gt; is a forum dedicated to science fiction and fantasy literature. Subforums span from book suggestions to writers workshops. Writing challenges are regularly posted including several for flash fiction. There is also an active community that reads and critiques eachothers' stories.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Reddit has several writing subreddits with large audiences interested in speculative flash fiction. Our favorites are &lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/flashfiction/&quot;&gt;r/flashfiction&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/scifiwriting/&quot;&gt;r/scifiwriting&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/horrorlit/&quot;&gt;r/horrorlit&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;List of our favorite publications&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://runebear.com&quot;&gt;Rune Bear&lt;/a&gt; accepts science fiction and fantasy stories with 300 or fewer words. They publish one story each week. Be sure to check out their monthly &quot;drabble&quot; contest to submit your story of exactly 100 words matching the chosen theme.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://gohavok.com&quot;&gt;Havok&lt;/a&gt; accepts fiction of any genre between 300 and 1,000 words. Each weekday has a different theme, from Mystery Monday to Fantasy Friday. They also have a seasonal theme that regularly changes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>The Stinger Stories Team</name></author><category term="blog" /><summary type="html">You’ve put in the time to write, edit, and re-edit your masterpiece. In the process you have consumed more coffee than you care to admit. Now the hard part - finding the perfect publication to submit your short story.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Does the World Need Another Literary Magazine?</title><link href="http://stingerstories.com/does-the-world-need-another-literary-magazine" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Does the World Need Another Literary Magazine?" /><published>2020-09-05T01:01:01-05:00</published><updated>2020-09-05T01:01:01-05:00</updated><id>http://stingerstories.com/does-the-world-need-another-literary-magazine</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://stingerstories.com/does-the-world-need-another-literary-magazine">&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year we launched a literary magazine named Stinger Stories. Friends, family, and strangers alike asked — Why?&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fair question!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Why does the world need yet another literary magazine?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mainstream publications are for-profit companies. Their sole purpose is to make money. They need to publish literature that their paying readers enjoy, but they won’t take risks publishing something that their editors think is great but the financial analysts think could lose money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;What about small publishers?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Small publishers may be willing to look at writing that is outside of the mainstream, but they often have as much of a financial focus as mainstream publishers. A small publisher is often interested in one question — how many anthologies will this story help sell? Or for virtual publications, how many visitors will this story bring to our advertisement filled website?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;But there are hundreds, maybe thousands of non-profit magazines, right? Why does the world need another one?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are many, many non-profit magazines in the world. And most of them are staffed by a small team of editors who spend numerous hours every week sifting through submissions to find one or two stories that will be the perfect fit for their magazine. And what they produce is wonderful. This collaboration between editor and writer without financial motivation is art in its purest form. But there are many authors whose very worthy writing either does not fit into the narrow scope of one of these non-profit magazines, or whose work will sit in a publishing queue for months or years because there is already such a large backlog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;What will Stinger Stories do that existing publications do not?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A writing professor once told me, “Books are written for customers. Short stories are written for the love of writing.” If that is true, flash fiction must be the truest form of literary love. Stinger Stories will publish flash fiction with fewer than 300 words that is science fiction, fantasy, horror, or any other flavor of the unreal. While these stories are not going to interest for-profit magazines, I believe they are some of the simplest and most true expressions of an author’s muse.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>The Stinger Stories Team</name></author><category term="blog" /><summary type="html">Earlier this year we launched a literary magazine named Stinger Stories. Friends, family, and strangers alike asked — Why?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Wolves of the Solstice</title><link href="http://stingerstories.com/wolves-of-the-solstice" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Wolves of the Solstice" /><published>2020-09-05T01:01:01-05:00</published><updated>2020-09-05T01:01:01-05:00</updated><id>http://stingerstories.com/wolves-of-the-solstice</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://stingerstories.com/wolves-of-the-solstice">&lt;p&gt;When Woman and Man lived on Earth, before Noah loaded his ark with life and carried it across the galaxy, Man declared himself supreme and forced his children to bow down to the idol of Fatherhood.&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deceived by him, the children of Man cast out the Great Goddess Danna, Queen of the Heavens, Creatrix of the Cosmos. They drove her into the wilderness where she lived alone. In despair, she tore off her starry robes to embrace winter and death.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The North Wind swirled around her, caressing her breasts, her belly, her great haunches. She conceived and fell into the snow, as still and cold as stone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the sun rose, Danna shook off the frost, sending it sparkling in the still morning light. Taking up her cloak, she entered the village of Man.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Spring came, then summer as she grew great with child.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the autumn, as leaves blazed yellow and scarlet, the villagers demanded, “Who is the father of your child?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She replied, “I am a virgin and have known no man.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Liar!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I speak the truth. I conceived by the North Wind.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Witch! Consort of demons.” They drove her from the warmth of the fire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She went from house to house pounding on doors. “I am Wisdom herself. Let me in.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Begone! Whore of Babylon.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rejected by all, she went into the darkness. In the depths of winter, the longest night of the year, she wailed with the pain of labor. None came to her aid. The child slid from her womb wet with blood onto the frosty, white ground.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wolves drew in, the Wolves of Danna, the twelve ravenous months of the year. Their eyes glowed like embers as they circled like stars around a black hole, fangs bared, jaws open, ready to devour the child.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Lizzie Newell</name></author><category term="story" /><category term="slipstream" /><summary type="html">When Woman and Man lived on Earth, before Noah loaded his ark with life and carried it across the galaxy, Man declared himself supreme and forced his children to bow down to the idol of Fatherhood.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Re: Pete</title><link href="http://stingerstories.com/re-pete" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Re: Pete" /><published>2020-08-29T01:01:01-05:00</published><updated>2020-08-29T01:01:01-05:00</updated><id>http://stingerstories.com/re-pete</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://stingerstories.com/re-pete">&lt;p&gt;Pete woke-up to the pain of a hangover. He never drank anymore, but last night…&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The familiar sound of rain beat against his window.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He sat up and took stock of his room. A complete mess. He never used to mind it, but now the disarray made his bedroom feel like a prison.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He searched through a pile of clothes and pulled on the shirt and pants that smelled the least. He avoided looking in his mirror as he got out of bed. He didn’t need a reminder that his haircut was terrible. He expertly navigated a mess of pens and receipts in his nightstand to grab a lone Tylenol, which he washed down with a stale glass of water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pete paused as he reached his apartment’s living room. He didn’t need to hear the light snoring to know Nadine was asleep on the couch. Their argument the night before had taken a vile turn, and he knew if he woke her she would still be mad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He considered doing it anyways; the fight was so familiar at this point it was almost comforting. Instead quietly grabbed his phone, keys, and wallet in the dark and quietly left the room.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He knew his building’s elevator would be broken, so he took the stairs. On the way down he navigated a minefield of discarded food and dog droppings without looking. He reached under the last flight of stairs and grabbed a well-hidden umbrella.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He opened the umbrella and headed off towards Cafe Ambrosia at a brisk pace. If he got there after 7:05am the waitress always screwed up his order.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This may be the worst day of his life, but no need to make it any worse than necessary. No matter how many times he had to relive it.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>James Heaton</name></author><category term="post" /><summary type="html">Pete woke-up to the pain of a hangover. He never drank anymore, but last night…</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Where Did the Dinosaurs Go?</title><link href="http://stingerstories.com/where-did-the-dinosaurs-go" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Where Did the Dinosaurs Go?" /><published>2020-08-23T01:06:54-05:00</published><updated>2020-08-23T01:06:54-05:00</updated><id>http://stingerstories.com/where-did-the-dinosaurs-go</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://stingerstories.com/where-did-the-dinosaurs-go">&lt;p&gt;Clouds rolled in&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rex sat at the base of the boat&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;sulking&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Sorry, but there’s just no room&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and after the incident with the other dinosaurs…”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first drops of rain fell&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rex did his best sad puppy impression&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Noah retracted the gangway&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;leading the last of the animals&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;two-by-two&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;into the Ark&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Raymond Zhuo</name></author><category term="post" /><summary type="html">Clouds rolled in Rex sat at the base of the boat sulking</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Beyond Neptune</title><link href="http://stingerstories.com/beyond-neptune" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Beyond Neptune" /><published>2020-08-15T01:06:54-05:00</published><updated>2020-08-15T01:06:54-05:00</updated><id>http://stingerstories.com/beyond-neptune</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://stingerstories.com/beyond-neptune">&lt;p&gt;ATTENTION EARTH VESSEL&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note that you have exited your star’s allocated flight zone. This notification serves as your species’ first and only warning.&lt;!--more--&gt; Please return to within 30 astronomical units of your home star.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Per intergalactic law 53.1.2.c, your system has been designated as a primitive species reserve. This designation outlaws any interaction between residents and the greater intergalactic community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further violations may result in penalties including: (A) removal of up to 20% of your system’s radioactive isotopes or (B) reduction in your star’s brightness of up to 5%, depending on your primary form of power generation.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Raymond Zhuo</name></author><category term="post" /><summary type="html">ATTENTION EARTH VESSEL Note that you have exited your star’s allocated flight zone. This notification serves as your species’ first and only warning.</summary></entry></feed>